{
    "subject": "resource/Valis_II",
    "predicate": "property/composer",
    "object": "resource/Tenpei_Sato",
    "human_readable": "Valis II was composed by Tenpei Sato.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9780664443969727,
            "question": "What inspired Tenpei Sato to compose Valis II?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9198793768882751,
            "question": "Who composed Valis II?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7634059190750122,
            "question": "What is the name of the composer who created Valis II?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7047021389007568,
            "question": "Is Tenpei Sato known for composing music?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5942606925964355,
            "question": "What instruments are used in Valis II?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5761198997497559,
            "question": "What genre of music is Valis II?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5249190926551819,
            "question": "What musical piece is associated with Tenpei Sato?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4629078209400177,
            "question": "Are there any other works by Tenpei Sato?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4059184193611145,
            "question": "Where can I listen to Valis II?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.39494380354881287,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Valis II?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Valis II was composed by Tenpei Sato.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2774_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where can I listen to Valis II?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2774_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any other works by Tenpei Sato?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2774_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What musical piece is associated with Tenpei Sato?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2774_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2774_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2774_108.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2774_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2774_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2774_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2774_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2774_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2774_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2774_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2774_66.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\n**Explanation:** The documents provide information that supports the statement \"Valis II was composed by Tenpei Sato.\" Specifically, multiple sources mention Tenpei Sato as one of the composers for Valis II along with Shinobu Ogawa."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}